itinfoz.com 2016-11-17

# PRIVACY POLICY

Cre8tive Magazine (“ **Cre8tiveMag** “) operates cre8tivemag.com and may operate other websites. It is Cre8tiveMag’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Personal privacy Plan**

We values our visitors privacy. Just how ever we do gather our visitors details to enhance our internet site and also to accumulate stats of site visitors information for our internet site we utilize Google Analytics. We never share our visitors info with third parties. Your personal privacy is extremely important to us. We use tool such Google Analytics to collect our viewers details such as IP addresses and also operating system usage.

**Net Based marketing**

Because Google sooner going to present advertisements based upon passions of customer, that is if you see sports associated websites frequently which have Google AdSense advertisements, you will certainly be organized as “sport enthusiast” category. This is Web Marketing technique from Google for this they collect some information which do not include your name, email-id, phone number, address or any sort of such details. You may read about that here.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, We collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Cre8tiveMag’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Cre8tiveMag’s visitors use its website. From time to time, We may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

We also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on cre8tivemag.com blogs/sites. We only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Cre8tiveMag’s websites choose to interact with Cre8tiveMag in ways that require Cre8tiveMag to gather personally-identifying information. Those who engage in transactions with Cre8tiveMag are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Cre8tiveMag collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Cre8tiveMag.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Cre8tiveMag may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Cre8tiveMag may display this information publicly or provide it to others. Cre8tiveMag does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Cre8tiveMag discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Cre8tiveMag’s behalf or to provide services available at Cre8tiveMag’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Cre8tiveMag discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Cre8tiveMag believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Cre8tiveMag, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Cre8tiveMag website and have supplied your email address, Cre8tiveMag may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Cre8tiveMag and our products.

**Cookies and also Web beacons**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Cre8tiveMag uses cookies to help Cre8tiveMag identify and track visitors, their usage of Cre8tiveMag website, and their website access preferences. Cre8tiveMag visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Cre8tiveMag’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Cre8tiveMag’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Here in our internet site you could have noted third party advertisements which may utilize Cookie on your computer to understand your routines, your IP address, your web browser, your operating system details. All these information will assist them to present advertisements fits to your interests. We have no accessibility to these data. You may disable those Cookies, however it impacts your interaction with this site.

**Business Transfers**

If Cre8tiveMag, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Cre8tiveMag goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Cre8tiveMag may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Advertisement**

We utilized to show advertisements from Google, Google likewise uses cookies to know your details. Google’s DART cookie enables them to show ads fit to your passion. You might opt out of DART cookie from here.

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Cre8tiveMag and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Most changes are likely to be minor, Cre8tiveMag may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Cre8tiveMag’s sole discretion. Cre8tiveMag encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.

Certain visitors to Cre8tiveMag’s websites choose to interact with Cre8tiveMag in ways that require Cre8tiveMag to gather personally-identifying information. Cre8tiveMag discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Cre8tiveMag’s behalf or to provide services available at Cre8tiveMag’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Cre8tiveMag discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Cre8tiveMag believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Cre8tiveMag, third parties or the public at large. Cre8tiveMag uses cookies to help Cre8tiveMag identify and track visitors, their usage of Cre8tiveMag website, and their website access preferences. Cre8tiveMag visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Cre8tiveMag’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Cre8tiveMag’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
